//Questions Table
// { question: 'My oven is cold', additional_info: "Won't turn on automatically", userId: 1, createdAt: new Date(), updatedAt: new Date() },
// { question: 'My dish tastes bland', additional_info: "I already added a ton of salt", userId: 1, createdAt: new Date(), updatedAt: new Date() },
// { question: 'My dough is not rising properly', additional_info: "Not sure what I did wrong", userId: 1, createdAt: new Date(), updatedAt: new Date() },
// { question: 'How much sugar go in cookies', additional_info: "I don't want them to turn out too sweet", userId: 1, createdAt: new Date(), updatedAt: new Date() },
// { question: 'What is al dente?', additional_info: "People keep using this work but idk what it means", userId: 1, createdAt: new Date(), updatedAt: new Date() },
// { question: 'How long does chicken last in the fridge?', additional_info: "Won't be home for a week", userId: 2, createdAt: new Date(), updatedAt: new Date() },
// { question: 'What type of wine goes well with steak?', additional_info: "I usually don't drink wine but I want to impress the in-laws", userId: 2, createdAt: new Date(), updatedAt: new Date() },
// { question: 'How long should I boil pasta for?', additional_info: "My pasta always turns out mushy", userId: 2, createdAt: new Date(), updatedAt: new Date() },
// { question: 'What temperature do I bake pizza at?', additional_info: "debating between 350 and 400 degrees", userId: 2, createdAt: new Date(), updatedAt: new Date() },
// { question: 'Should I cook steak on the pan or grill?', additional_info: "I bought these wagyu steaks from Costco and not sure how to cook them", userId: 2, createdAt: new Date(), updatedAt: new Date() },

//Answers Table
// { answer: 'Try checking you outlet', questionId: 1, userId: 2, createdAt: new Date(), updatedAt: new Date() },
// { answer: 'Add pepper, duh', questionId: 1, userId: 2, createdAt: new Date(), updatedAt: new Date() },
// { answer: 'add less water', questionId: 1, userId: 2, createdAt: new Date(), updatedAt: new Date() },
// { answer: 'try a cup for a serving size of 12', questionId: 1, userId: 2, createdAt: new Date(), updatedAt: new Date() },
// { answer: 'basically chewy pasta', questionId: 1, userId: 2, createdAt: new Date(), updatedAt: new Date() },
// { answer: 'a week', questionId: 2, userId: 1, createdAt: new Date(), updatedAt: new Date() },
// { answer: 'try any red wine', questionId: 2, userId: 1, createdAt: new Date(), updatedAt: new Date() },
// { answer: 'depends on how much you are boiling, maybe 5-10 minutes', questionId: 2, userId: 1, createdAt: new Date(), updatedAt: new Date() },
// { answer: 'definitely 400', questionId: 2, userId: 1, createdAt: new Date(), updatedAt: new Date() },
// { answer: 'both work, but I like pan better', questionId: 2, userId: 1, createdAt: new Date(), updatedAt: new Date() },

